# Layan A. Alamri

Computer Science Graduate

+966504152617



llayan2213@gmail.com



28 April 2001



Khobar, Saudi Arabia

# **Career Objective**

An ambitious Computer Science graduate with passion for programming and ability to transform ideas into effective solutions.

My ultimate goal is to develop my software skills and professional experience by working with experienced computer scientists in an established company, in addition to applying my current programming skills in adding value to the company.

#### Education

2019 - 2022 Advanced Diploma in Computer Science

Imam Abdulrahman Bin Faisal University

GPA: 3.69

#### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic - Native

English

# COMPUTER & SOFT SKILLS

o Java, C#

o HTML, PHP, CSS

o SOL

Leadership

Team work

Creativity

# **Work Experience**

2022 - Now Undergraduate Entrepreneurship Camps

Smart Parking System Project

2020 - 2021 Innovation Program for Entrepreneurs

Training and qualification for leadership and innovation

November 2020 - May 2021

### **Projects**

2022 Smart Parking System Project

Eastern Hackathon (March, 2022)

2022 Paper Storm Application

Graduation Project (January - May, 2022)